
// Array of objects
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: 'What is the sum of 130+125+191?',
        options: ['335','456','446','426'],
        answer: 446
      },
    
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "If we minus 712 from 1500, how much do we get?",
        
        options:['788','778','768','758'],
        answer: 788
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:'50 times of 8 is equal to:',
        options:['80','400','800','4000'],
        answer: 400
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:'110 divided by 10 is:',
        options:['11','10','5','None of the above'],
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:'20+(90÷2) is equal to:',
        options:['50','55','60','65'],
        answer: 60
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:'The product of 82 and 5 is:',
        options:['400','410','420','None of the above'],
        answer: 410
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:'Find the missing terms in multiple of 3: 3, 6, 9, __, 15',
        options:['10','11','12','13'],
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:'Solve 24÷8+2.',
        options:['5','6','8','12',''],
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:'What is the next prime number after 5?',
        options:['6','7','9','11'],
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:'Solve: 300 – (150×2)',
        options:['150','100','50','0'],
        answer: 0
    },
]